eupedia.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy & Cookie Information - Eupedia

**Eupedia.com** is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of our privacy policies, please do not hesitate to [contact us](https://www.eupedia.com/contact/).

## What information we hold about you

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

  * Your name or username.
  * Your email address.
  * Your IP address.
  * Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * You register as a member on this site.
  * You fill out our contact form.
  * You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
  * You fill out fields on your profile.

## How your personal information is used

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
  * Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

Eupedia.com will never sell or distribute email addresses and/or other personally identifying information to third parties without your explicit permission, nor use it for unapproved commercial purposes. Our policy is to protect the privacy and confidentiality of our visitors and users.

## Use of Cookies

**This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit to identify your device, or you when you have logged in on the Eupedia Forum. They are widely used to enhance the functionality of the website by storing your preferences, to improve the performance of our website, and to provide you with a better user experience. You can find more information about cookies on [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). You can learn how to delete or disable cookies [here](https://www.wikihow.com/Disable-Cookies).

  * Google analytics: to generates traffic statistic and better understand the usage and popularity of various pages so we can improve the site for our visitors. These cookies do not contain personally identifiable information (PII), for example user names or e-mail addresses. You can choose whether to allow Google analytics cookies using the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). 

  * AddThis & Shareaholic: sharing buttons used to spread content across the web making it easy for visitors to bookmark and share with other people. Provide statistics about bookmarking and sharing activity of users, and generates ranking about popular and trending content. 

  * Disqus: a comment and discussion management platform that allows publishers to moderate conversations regarding content, across various social media sites. They also provide track backs and analytics reporting. This cookie is used in order to log in and post a comment. 

We also use cookies for targeted advertising and campaign tracking, notably DoubleCclick (Google), Quantcast (Disqus by-product) and ScoreCard (Disqus by-product). These cookies are used by third parties to gather and send information to other websites so that they can present you with adverts that you might be interested in.

## Rights

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please contact us. If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may contact us to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please contact us if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.
